



SKILLS

- HubSpot CRM
- · MS office
- Cold calling
- Communication
- Sales Expertise
- Academic Advising
- · Career Counseling
- Issue Resolution
- Key Performance Indicators (KPI)
- Strategic Planning
- Call Center Operations
- Client Support
- Performance Improvement
- Analytical Thinking
- Customer service
- Academic Monitoring
- Multitasking Abilities
- Excellent Communication
- Salesforce CRM Experience

LANGUAGES

English: Bilingual or Proficient (C2) Hindi: Bilingual or Proficient (C2) Spanish: Beginner (A1)

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Excellent social skills, teamwork, creative direction and the ability to work in different environments. 2+ years experience on marketing, sales and communication. Highly analytical and results oriented with good communication and negotiable skills. comfortable working under pressure. Open to learn new skills and knowledge. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Hardworking and passionate job seeker with strong organizational skills eager to secure position. Ready to help team achieve company goals.

WORK HISTORY

Academic Advisor, 08/2023 to 09/2023 Global Alumni - Madrid

- · Worked for University of Miami Herbert business school as Academic advisor to professionals.
- · Answered lead inquiries and resolved problems related to curriculum and course prerequisites.
- · Conducted academic advisement services for leads on reoccurring basis to maintain educational progression.
- Provided support and guidance to leads experiencing academic and personal troubles.
- · Mentored students, offering advice and support on topic selection, appropriateness and academic value.
- · Received and reviewed transcripts to determine eligibility for admission to university or specific programs.
- Assessed data gathering methods for validity and reliability purposes.

Lead generation executive, 05/2022 to 05/2023 Neo kinetics Pvt Ltd - Mumbai

Research, track, maintain and update leads and conduct market surveys to obtain information about potential leads.

- Make outgoing calls to develop new business.
- Provide accurate and timely information to management.
- · Develop a strong knowledge of the company's products and services in order to facilitate the sales process
- Used tools like CRM to create healthy relation with clients.
- Built relationships with customers and community to promote long term business growth.
- Contributed to team objectives in fast-paced environment.
- · Informed customers of promotions to increase sales productivity and volume.
- Worked with sales team to collaboratively reach targets, consistently meeting or exceeding personal quotas.
- Met existing customers to review current services and expand sales opportunities.
- · Monitored service after sale and implemented quick and effective problem resolutions.
- · Identified new business opportunities through cold calling, networking, marketing and prospective database leads.

Sales Executive/ Business development executive, 07/2020 to 10/2021 Srijan medi solutions Pvt ltd - Indore

- · Working with planning and dedication.
- · Searching for new clients with the help of online and offline platform.
- · Developed and presented valuable sales presentations to potential customers to highlight features and benefits of products.
- Trained new employees on customer service, money handling and organizing strategies.
- Consulted with businesses to supply accurate product and service information.
- Stayed current on company offerings and industry trends.
- · Quoted prices, credit terms and other bid specifications. · Recorded accurate and efficient records in customer database.
- Taking follow ups from existing customers.
- · Attended monthly sales meetings and quarterly sales trainings.
- Evaluated costs against expected market price points and set structures to achieve profit targets.

Marketing coordinator, 06/2019 to 08/2019 Shakti Pumps pvt ltd - Indore

- Tracked and reported on marketing campaign responses.
- Conducted market research to identify new opportunities and target markets.

Intern, 01/2018 to 03/2018 Samosys technologies Pvt ltd - Indore

- Analyzed problems and worked with teams to develop solutions.
- · Sorted and organized files, spreadsheets, and reports.
- Interacted with customers by phone, email, or in-person to provide information.

EDUCATION

MBA: Marketing, 05/2020

Medi Caps University - Indore , India

GPA: 8.85

BBA: Marketing, 05/2018

Devi Ahilya Vishwavidyalaya university - Indore, India

GPA: 70%, GPA: 64%

CERTIFICATIONS

Digital Marketing certificate